comfi.com 2007-06-08

# Phone Cards Online: make calls for less. ComFi.com

Comfi.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of users of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for users.   
The purpose of this Comfi.com privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Comfi.com, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit Comfi.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. This privacy policy applies to the Comfi.com site. 

## Information About All Comfi.com Users

In general, our site automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to Comfi.com and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This aggregate data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, Comfi.com uses a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through these cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our Comfi.com partners about how our members, collectively, use Comfi.com. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well. Finally, Comfi.com, its advertisers and ad servers may also use cookies, as well as small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs," to determine on an anonymous basis which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them, but do not use these technologies to collect personally identifiable information unless you give us permission to do so. 

## Information About You

If you are an Comfi.com member, when you access Comfi.com you may obtain access to features of the Comfi.com online service that contain personal information. Additionally, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service, like Comfi.com phone services, or when you order a product. We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address or screen name, billing address, credit card number -- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for the product or service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not. We also use cookie technology in order to improve your experience, including to remember your preferences or customized settings when you use Comfi.com and its related services, and to authenticate your access to your personal information. 

## Disclosure

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Comfi.com or information that you may give us on Comfi.com, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. Comfi.com may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. And, as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of Comfi.com. 

## Children on Comfi.com

Comfi.com takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of young people using our services, and encourages you to participate in your child's experience in cyberspace. Comfi.com is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children. For parents who are Comfi.com members, Comfi.com recommends that parents review important safety tips before your child explores the Internet, and use Parental Controls. 

## Comfi.com Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy for Comfi.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

Questions regarding the above statement should be directed to ComFi Inc. for clarification.

Contact:

ComFi Inc.,  
PO Box 81362  
Wellesley, MA 02481   
Last updated: September 5, 2006
